<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>squ4r00t&#39;s</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on squ4r00t&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extended Euclidian Algorithm Explained</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ext_euclid_alg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ext_euclid_alg/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I explain the Euclidian Algorithm (+extended) and how to implement them in python.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;prerequisite-modulus-operator&#34;&gt;Prerequisite: Modulus Operator&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, we need to understand the modulus operator.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The modulus operator, often represented by the percent character (&lt;code&gt;%&lt;/code&gt;) in many programming languages, returns the rest of the division between 2 operands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, let&amp;rsquo;s say we have 2 integers &lt;code&gt;a=5&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;b=2&lt;/code&gt;. Then &lt;code&gt;a mod b&lt;/code&gt; will be equal to &lt;code&gt;1&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPS: A convenient way of scanning through network pivots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/portscanning-through-pivots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/portscanning-through-pivots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried scanning ports on a machine present in an internal network through a pivot machine, you might have noticed that it can be very slow at times and that the results of the scan aren&amp;rsquo;t always very reliable (often times missing open ports :/).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once solution that comes to mind might be to transfer nmap (or another port scanner) on the pivot machine and then run the scan from there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTB - Oouch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/htb/oouch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/htb/oouch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oouch is a hard difficulty Linux machine featuring web applications that use the OAuth authorization framework. Absence of a CSRF Token is leveraged to link an administrative account to our account, providing access to sensitive information. This information is used to register a new client application and steal the authorization code. This code is used to gain an access token, which provides unrestricted access to user resources. A misconfigured DBus server is then exploited through uWSGI in order to execute code in the context of root.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTB - CTF</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/htb/ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/htb/ctf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CTF is an insane difficulty Linux box with a web application using LDAP based authentication. The application is vulnerable to LDAP injection but due to character blacklisting the payloads need to be double URL encoded. After enumeration, a token string is found, which is obtained using boolean injection. Using the token an OTP can be generated, which allows for execution of commands. After establishing a foothold, a cron can be exploited to gain sensitive information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
